Today I'm making a video from the Tesla.
It's in self-driving mode. It's why I
don't need to have my hands on the
steering wheel. It drives itself, all
that. But I do have to stay kind of
attentive to the road to make sure that
everything is safe. That said, what I
want to talk about is the best way to
make sure that you get the best clients
in your business. One of the biggest
problems that happens when people are
building an online coaching business and
they're trying to run ads, they're
trying to create content is that they
think that everybody could be a great
client for them, that everybody could be
a great fit to work with them. And
unfortunately, that's not true. As what
you want to do is in your marketing, in
your sales copy, in your offers, you
want to repel the wrong people. You want
to make sure that it not only attracts
the right people because that's
important to do, but that it looks to be
the thing that like they do not want if
it's the wrong person. That it's very
obviously not made for them. And so,
when we're just starting out in our
businesses, sometimes it can be a
temptation to be like, well, I want to
work with everybody. I want to be
available to everybody. And
unfortunately, that's not a great thing
to do. But I can tell you some of my
worst business clients, and I've had
some pretty bad ones. I have some really
great ones, too. They're incredible. The
clients I work with every single day in
our coaching group are just some of the
most amazing people in the world. But
I've also had some that are just not
like I should have just said no. I
should have said it's probably not a
good fit to work with me because they
were draining. They were demanding. They
weren't teachable. They thought they
knew better than what I was sharing as
the expert. And all that to say, it was
just not worth even the the dollars that
they paid. And so realize that in your
coaching business, part of niching down
is making sure that you are attracting
the right people and repelling the wrong
ones. And so that has to do with the
words that you put in your ads. It has
to do with the words that you put on
your landing page, your sales copy. How
do you say things? How are you
communicating to people? And when you
can do this the right way, it will make
sure that you have the right people
coming into your ecosystem. Now, here's
one of the best ways to do that. Okay,
one of the things is that I will put at
the top of my landing page, I'll
actually write some sales copy out and
it will say this is for coaches, course
creators, trainers, mentors, thought
leaders, and then I will even put if you
are in network marketing, e-commerce,
uh just any of the other industries that
usually come and want me to show them
what to do. uh you're a SAS product, you
know, this is probably not going to be a
good fit for you to learn from. I I ran
a campaign once and I didn't put that on
there and I had so many real estate
agents. And then check it out. They were
disappointed because my content wasn't
real estate focused. Well, I'm not I'm a
real estate agent. You're teaching about
coaches. Why are you doing that? Or I
did this one thing. It was all for
coaches, but I didn't specify that it
was online. that it was for specifically
online mentors and coaches. And so I had
a bunch of people that were like, well,
I want to do offline. I don't want to do
anything on the internet. So now it's
like, okay, this is for online mentors
and coaches, people who want to use
Facebook ads. They want to generate
leads. They want to create a lead
magnet. They want to know how to get
hundreds of leads that then convert into
clients. And by the way, if that's you,
if you're somebody that wants to know
how to use Facebook and Instagram ads to
generate leads that actually turn into
clients, you're a good fit for what I
offer. You're a good fit for the things
that I do. You can go check out a link
below and try out my mentorship program
for 14 days and see the difference that
it makes the community that we have.
I've been doing this in this industry
for over 22 years. I've been in the
industry before most people even knew
what online coaching was. And I've been
doing this type of a thing. And so what
I share isn't from theory. It comes from
direct experience of working with
thousands of coaches and mentors and
course creators successfully to see what
works and what doesn't. And so if you
want to get the best clients, this is my
number one thing that I share with
people. You got to repel the wrong
people and you got to attract the right
people. Another great way to repel
people is just by being yourself. I meet
so often coaches and mentors trying to
turn themselves into what they think
their prospects want. Here's a great
example of that. This video right here,
it's not super polished. I'm in my car.
I got like an overgrown beard a little
bit. Some of my videos I got like a like
a nice beard and others is like this.
My clients who watch me and follow me
like they they don't see that as a
reason to not trust me. I will tell you
something. There is a whole demographic
of people that are out there that
literally how I look,
how I dress, the t-shirt that I'm
filming in my self-driving car, the fact
that I own a Tesla, whatever,
whether you like Elon Musk or not is is
irrelevant.
They won't want to listen to me because
of that. And so the fact that I even put
those things in there, like I talk
openly about the fact that I enjoy
playing video games, that I that I
have two kids, that I am not about the
hustle culture, that I'm not about
burnout and striving to get results in
your business. And those things will
either attract or repel people by you
being honest.
Okay, let's talk about integrity here.
Let's talk about being honest.
The more honest you are and real and
just you're just you. You're not trying
to put a persona or a facade together to
get people to like you. The more you do
that, the better results you are going
to get in your business.
You're just going to get better results
overall. It's just going to work out
better for you in the end.
You are just going to have better
clients. And
well, Jeremiah, what about making money?
You're going to make way more money,
too. You're actually going to have way
more of the right clients, the right
people, not just anybody. And here's
what I do is I pay attention to what do
my best clients, and I think about my
best clients in two ways. they get the
most results
and they stick with me the longest. They
stick around because they're getting so
much value from working with me. So,
from a financial standpoint and from a
business standpoint and from a results
standpoint and from a testimonial
standpoint,
what do those people have in common? I
go into what's called pattern
recognition mode. I'm recognizing the
pattern of what all of those people have
in common with each other
and then letting that determine, okay,
those are the people that I want to work
with. Those are the people that I want
to attract in my business. And so then I
gear and I structure and I design all
the stuff that I do in my business
around
those things,
around those exact things. What are the
things that are determining
if somebody is a good fit to work with
me is if they get the most results and
and I'm going to be straight up here if
they're spending money with me. Because
listen, I got a lot of people, they
watch my YouTube. I got a lot of people
who watch my content. They're great
people. I love you. But if you're not
becoming a client of mine, I'm not going
to be necessarily gearing or designing
my stuff in a way that is probably going
to help you as much. I'm only focused on
those that produce an economic financial
result for my business and that I get
the most results for. And when those two
things come into alignment,
those are the most important parts. What
makes me the most money
and gets them that are giving me the
money the most result.
And I marry those together and and
that's what I think is is the highest
level of integrity way to do things and
the most profitable. Okay. So, like put
blinders on of anything that is outside
of the range or the realm of what those
things are. Just put absolute blinders
on completely. Stop paying attention to
anything that is going to distract you
from working with the right people, from
connecting with those right people, from
really meeting. Okay, who are those
people that I am meant to work with,
that I am meant to have in my space,
that are supposed to be in my ecosystem,
that are going to become my best
clients.
And when you can do this, you will make
far more money in your business than you
ever thought possible. you will spend
far less time trying to I can look back
at the times when I wasn't doing this
when I was trying to validate myself to
people when I was way too concerned
about trying to make sure I said
everything right and and that it all
that and that by doing all the right
stuff that that would produce clients
and and it didn't it didn't get me the
results that I wanted. It didn't make me
the kind of money that I wanted to make.
It actually lost me more money in the
end. It actually produced far greater
problems for me overall in my business,
in my growth, and in what I was trying
to accomplish by trying to control that
aspect of it. And so what I do is I am
not necessarily trying to control that
aspect of it. I am working to make sure
that okay the right people I'm going to
attract them but I'm also going to
simultaneously repel the ones who are
not a good fit. Do this it will work.
Follow what I share and you will get
results. I can't wait to hear what
happens for you in your business when
you apply this and when you start doing
what I'm saying. We'll talk soon
everybody. Have a good one.